bestway.com.pk 2013-03-24

# Bestway Cement - Privacy Policy

### This Privacy Policy was last updated on 1st July, 2011.

Bestway Cement Limited (“Bestway”) respects the privacy of those who visit our site. Please read our Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) carefully so that you can understand how we collect and use the personal information that you may provide to us and the terms and conditions which govern the use of, and copying from, this site.

By using this site and/or submitting your personal information, you signify your assent to our Policy. If you do not agree to our Policy or any part of it, please do not use this site. We reserve the right, at our absolute discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Policy at any time.

We want to be very clear: We do not obtain personal information about you other than that which you choose to provide, and we will not sell, rent, trade or otherwise disclose the personal information you provide to anyone outside of the Bestway Group of companies and their advertising and promotional agencies and consultants, except in those specific instances where you expressly give us permission to do so.

### What does this Policy cover?

This Policy covers our use of your personal information which may be collected through or in connection with this site. For the purposes of this Policy, "this site" means the whole of this website except links provided to websites of other Bestway Group companies or third party websites.  

Third party or other Bestway Group companies’ websites may contain Privacy Policies which may be different from this Policy. If you access any other website through this site then please check the privacy policy of each website which you visit. You must not assume that this Policy applies to all Bestway Group companies’ websites or third party websites to which this site provides links.

###  Who is responsible for the personal information collected on this site?

Bestway controls any personal information which may be collected on, through or in connection with this site.

###  Special Notice - if you are a minor

If you are a minor please do not send us your personal information (for example, your name, address, email address and telephone/fax numbers). If you are a minor and you wish to ask a question or use this site in anyway which requires you to submit your personal information please ask your parent or guardian to do so on your behalf.

###  Information collection and use

We may collect and use personal information (including name, address, telephone/fax numbers and email address) in order to:

  * respond to requests or queries submitted by you
  * process applications or orders submitted by you
  * create products or services that may meet your needs 
  * anticipate and resolve problems with any products or services provided to you 
  * administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement we have with you

As part of the information and/or products and services offered to you through this site, the information you provide to us may be transferred to outside Pakistan. For example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located outside Pakistan or one of our service providers is located in a country outside Pakistan. These countries may not have data protection laws similar to those which may exist in Pakistan. If transfer of your information outside Pakistan in this way is required, we may not be able to ensure that your privacy rights continue to be protected. In addition, if you use this site while you are outside Pakistan, your information may be transferred outside Pakistan in order to be able to provide you with a service or information. 

Except as set out in this Policy, we will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless we are legally entitled or required to do so (for example, if required to do so by legal process or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime) or if we believe that such action is necessary to protect and/or defend our rights, property or personal safety and those of our users/customers etc.

###  Providing you with additional information and sharing your information ****

From time to time we would like to use your personal information for purposes other than as set out in the above section. We believe that these additional uses will be of benefit to you. However, we understand that you may not wish us to use your information in this way. We will not use your information for the purposes set out below if you have indicated that you do not wish us to use your information in this way when submitting the information. Additionally, if at any time you wish us to stop using your information for any or all of the below purposes, please let us know. We will stop the use of your information for such purposes as soon as it is reasonably possible to do so. In such case we will, however, continue to use your personal information for the purposes set out in the above section for as long as it is reasonable to do so. 

From time to time we would like to use the information you supply to us for: 

  * market research and tracking of sales data
  * informing you about our products and services, which may include contacting you by telephone, fax or email
  * giving the information to Bestway’s affiliate offices and companies, which may be located outside Pakistan, to enable them to send you information which may be of interest to you.

In addition, from time to time we would like to give your name, address and e-mail and any other personal information you supply to us to selected third parties, which may be located outside Pakistan. These third parties may use this information for:

  * market research and tracking of sales data 
  * sending you information about their products and services
  * giving the information to their affiliate offices and companies to enable them to send you information which may be of interest to you.

### Collection of non-personal information

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you such as the type of internet browser you use or the website from which you linked to this site. We may also aggregate details which you have submitted to the site (for example, your age, your gender and the city where you live). You cannot be identified from this information and it may only be used to assist us in providing an effective service on this site. We may from time to time supply third parties with this non-personal or aggregated data for uses in connection with this site.

###  The use of cookies

We may store some information (commonly known as a "cookie") on your computer when you look at this site. We are able to read these cookies for information purposes when you revisit this site. The type of information we collect as a result of a cookie being accepted by you is specific to your PC and includes the IP address, the date and time the PC visited this site, what parts of this site were looked at and whether the web pages requested were delivered successfully. This information is anonymous and it represents a computer rather than a person. 

We use the cookie information to improve our knowledge of the use of this site and to enable us to be able to ascertain whether this site is operating at an optimal level. This allows us to enhance our web offerings to you and to provide an enjoyable and an innovative online experience. 

You can erase or block this information by changing the settings on your computer (please refer to your help screens or manuals). If you do erase or block this information you may not be able to utilise some features of this site.

###  Chat rooms, notice boards, newsgroups

If at any time this site offers any chat rooms, notice board facilities, newsgroups etc. we may collect the information that you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this privacy policy. Please note that we cannot be responsible for other parties' use of the personal information which you make available to such third parties through any chat room, notice board, newsgroup etc on this site. Please be careful about what personal information you disclose in this way.

###  E-mail, Feedback and Forum Facilities 

If at any time this site offers any e-mail, feedback or forum facilities, we may collect the information which you disclose. Such information will be used in accordance with this Policy.

###  Keeping our records accurate

Wherever applicable and practical, we aim to keep our information about you as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details you may have supplied us with, please contact us as set out below.

###  Security of your personal data ****

We have implemented technology and policies with the objective of protecting your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use and will update these measures as new technology becomes available, as appropriate.

### Use of your personal information submitted to other web sites

We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if: 

  * you accessed the third party website using links from this site; or 
  * you linked to this site from a third party website

We recommend that you check the privacy policy of each website you visit and contact the owner or operator of such website if you have any concerns or questions.

###  Submission of others personal information ****

From time to time this site may ask you to provide personal details of your family or friends, for example, so that we can send them details of our products and services. Before providing such information, please ensure that you have obtained their consent to their personal information being used in this way. We will not use these details in any manner which is incompatible with this Policy.

###  Will this privacy policy change?

From time to time we may make changes to this Policy. Please check back on a regular basis for any changes we may make to this Policy. Your continued use of this site following the posting of changes to this Policy will be treated as your acceptance of the changes and your permission for disclosures referred to in this Policy.

###  How you can contact us ****

If you would like to contact Bestway about this Policy, you can do so by emailing the Webmaster at:  [webmaster@bestway.com.pk](mailto:webmaster@bestway.com.pk)

Thank you for visiting our site.
